

ANAMUL HASAN RIFAT

Address

Dubai International city
United Arab Emirates

Contact

+971 0569768483 ritzrifat5@gmail.com

Date of Birth

10.10.2001

Twitter

ritz rifat

Instagram

ritz_rifat

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Microsoft Office - Word, Excel, Power point

Web Developing - Html.Css.Js.

Data Entry - Typing

LANGUAGES

English.Hindi, Bangla -

PROFILE

I am a self motivated, energetic individual. I work effectively both within a team and individually using my own initiative. I believe that i will be an individual asset to any organization giving my experience, dedication and the great pride that i take in my work.

EDUCATION

October 2021

Modon Mohon Collage

BBA(Hons) in Management

June 2018 - April 2021

Sylhet Government College

H.S.C

January 2016 - February 2018

Sylhet Government Model School &College

5.5.C

EXPERIENCE

December 2020 - December 2021

Rajmahal Sweets And Fire Foods

Cashiei

Responsibilities: Processing and receiving payments, issuing receipts to customers

as they leave with their purchases.

Scan goods and ensure pricing is accurate.

Cross-sell products and introduce new ones;

August 2018 - October 2020

Nashua Pharma

Cashier

Responsibilities: Processing and receiving payments whether cash or credit, issue

receipts, refunds, change or tickets.

SKILLS

- ✓ Good communication written and oral skills
- ✓ Excellent conceptual and analytical skills
- ✓ Effective interpersonal skills
- ✓ Internet and Research
- ✓ Strong and quick acquiring new technologies.
- ✓ Strong Verbal and written communication skills.
- ✓ Ability to network with client at every level.

HOBBY









Technology

Tennis

Chess

Tavels